PAMELA RANDHAN

3048 SE 37th Avenue, Okeechobee, Florida 34974 Mobile: (772) 501-9795 Email: pamelamarie76@yahoo.com

My diverse experience along with a desire to use critical thinking skills brings opportunities to learn, strategize and prioritize to accomplish multiple tasks while staying calm under pressure. Accountable, well organized, detail-oriented and a conscientious self-starter. Personable interactions with clients provide customer service skills to utilize with my diligent work ethic.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Family Dollar, Okeechobee, FL

August 2018 - Present

Assistant Manager

- Support the Store Manager with daily operations and management tasks in compliance with SOP
- Accountable of cash management and bank deposits
- Accountable of store and inventories accesses / internal audits.
- Prepare and finalize employee schedules.
- Direct training of store team members including cash handling, deposits and store opening/closing operations.
- Maintain customer service standards with complete and comprehensive knowledge of store layout and merchandise.

Hard Time Bail Bonds, Okeechobee, Florida Intern - Limited Liability Surety Agent

November 2017-June 2018

- intern Limited Liability Surety Agent
- Accurately and efficiently prepare all bonds for clients.
- Collect bond premium payments and review contracts to determine bond requirement.
- Set up and maintain all account files.

D & D Global Trans. Fort Pierce, FL

January 2012-February 2018

Part Time - Office Manager/Bookkeeper

- Process all accounts payable and receivable transactions and reconciled bank accounts.
- Oversee and monitor all Payroll functions including preparing operational spreadsheets with efficiency.
- Coordinate timely delivery while preparing schedules and coordinate with dispatch.
- Monitor and maintain office supplies and equipment inventory.

East Coast Sod & Landscape, Fort Pierce, FL

August 2012-March 2017

June 2005-June 2008

- Part Time Office Manager/Bookkeeper
- Process all accounts payable/receivables, Construction billing, payroll and bank account reconciliation.
- Assist employees with HR duties such as benefit enrollment and payroll.
- Provide estimates, plan take offs, build spreadsheets and efficiently complete construction billing.

APAC Southeast, Inc, Winter Haven, FL

June 2003 - June 2005

Administrative Assistant

- Preparation of monthly FDOT Design Build Project estimates.
- Organize and complete construction documents, Construction billing, spreadsheets.
- Enter all CQR and LIMS on FDOT Mainframe.
- Conduct all orientations and training of new employees.

Grimes Heating and A/C, Fort Pierce, FL

June 2000-December 2002

Office Manager/Bookkeeper

- Process all accounts payable/receivables, Construction billing, payroll and bank account reconciliation
- Payroll, benefit enrollment, spreadsheets
- Maintenance schedule and supervised file clerk.

EDUCATION

• Fort Pierce Central High School, Fort Pierce, FL Diploma, June 1994

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

- Proficient in Microsoft Office Suite (Word, Excel, Outlook, PowerPoint).
- Experienced with QuickBooks Pro and QuickBooks Online

CERTIFICATION

• TO235 – Limited Surety Agent – Florida Bail Bond School